question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The game 'Battlefield 1' takes place during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the game 'Subnautica', a 'Spadefish' will attack you.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game 'Overwatch' on July 19th, 2016.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In 'RuneScape', one must complete the 'Dragon Slayer' quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In 'Resident Evil 4', the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
